Finding Aid for the Louis B. Schnauber (Film Music Society) Collection PASC-M.0157
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Land of the Birds. The Nightingale, 1909; Carl Fischer Inc.; Klein, Manuel; Thomas, Ludomir (Box 16, Folder 1191)
- Nigger in the Barnyard, 1891; 15 parts (Box 14)
- Nigger-Toe (Box 1, Folder 73)
- Night on the Water (Box 3, Folder 239)
  Also composed by George & Bert Clarke and Ellery Rand.
- Nights of Gladness (Box 7, Folder 635)
- Nights of Gladness (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Ninette (Box 3, Folder 275)
- Nippon (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Nipponese (Box 6, Folder 554)
- No Me Olvides = Forget Me Not, 1921; Belwin, Inc.; Lapham, Claude; Schoenfeld, William Charles (Box 16, Folder 1189)
- Nocturne, 1909; 30 p. (Box 2, Folder 120)
- Nocturne, 1916; Bergé, Irénée; De Koven, Reginald; G. Schirmer, Inc. (Box 16, Folder 1204)
- Nocturne no. 1 for Flute and Clarinet, Behr, Franz; Carl Fischer Inc.; Staats, C.L. (Box 16, Folder 1201)
- Nocturne, op. 15, no. 1, 1919; Chopin, Frédéric; Glazounow, Aleksandr Konstantinovich; Roberts, Charles J. (Box 16, Folder 1218)
- Nocturne in F, 1910; Carl Fischer Inc.; Tobani, Theo. M. (Box 16, Folder 1209)
- Nocturnal Piece (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Nola, 1916; Sam Fox Publishing Co.; Zamecnik, J.S.; Arndt, Felix (Box 16, Folder 1196)
- Norma: Duet (Hear Me Norma), 1916; Bellini; Carl Fischer Inc.; Lake, Mayhew (Box 16, Folder 1195)
- A Norwegian Episode, 1901 (Box 12, Folder 978)
- N'Orleans (Box 3, Folder 297)
- Northern Impressions, Woodland Fairy and Carnival (Box 12, Folder 975)
- Norwegian Dance (Box 11, Folder 967)
- Norwegian Folk Song, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 977)
- Nothing Seems The Same, 1926; 16 p. (Box 2, Folder 126)
  Work also composed by Jesse Greer.
- Notoriety (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Notturno, op. 9, no. 2, Carl Fischer Inc.; Chopin, Frédéric; Moses, Theo. (Box 16, Folder 1207)
- Novelletta, op. 16, 1913; Carl Fischer Inc.; D'Ambrosio, A. (Alfredo); Dumont, Adolphe (Box 16, Folder 1188)
- Novellette, 1914; Marquis, Jean Jaques; Carl Fischer Inc.; Lake, Mayhew (Box 16, Folder 1193)
- Novelty Hurry (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Nuit et Lamour = Night and Love, Holmès, Augusta Mary Anne; Jungnickel, Ross (Box 16, Folder 1206)
  On item: Artist's Orchestra Repertoir, no. 46.
- Nursery Rhymes, 1922; 18 p. (Box 2, Folder 111)
- Nut Cracker Suite. Valse des Fleurs (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Oberon Overture, 1915; 15 parts (Box 13)
- Oh! How She Could Yacki Hacki Wicki Wacki Woo (Box 5, Folder 461)
  Lyrics also composed by Charles McCarron
- Oh Oh Ma Baby (Box 2, Folder 200)
  "A Hawaiian La La."
- Oh! What A Gal was Mary (Box 8, Folder 736)
- Old Chestnuts (Box 7, Folder 649)
- Old Folks at Home (Paraphrase) (Box 11, Folder 945)
- The Old Grey Mare (Box 8, Folder 742)
- The Old Refrain (Box 3, Folder 246)
- Old Well, The, 1916; Bendix, Theo. (Theodore); Lake, Mayhew; M. Witmark & Sons (Box 16, Folder 1203)
  On item: Country scenes no. 7.
- Ole Virginny (Box 10, Folder 907)
- Olive's Brow (Box 4, Folder 363)
- On Desert Sands, 1913 (Box 9, Folder 840)
- On Miami Shore (Box 3, Folder 293)
- On a Moonlight Night, 1915; J. Fischer; Rhys-Herbert, W.; Wiegand, John (Box 16, Folder 1205)
- On the Green (Box 7, Folder 639)
- On the Mountain, 1921; Belwin, Inc.; Frommel, H.C.; Schoenfeld, William Charles (Box 16, Folder 1192)
- On the Sky Line (Box 7, Folder 588)
- One Fleeting Hour (Box 7, Folder 589)
- One Fleeting Hour, 1915; Lee, Dorothy; Sam Fox Publishing Co.; Zamecnik, J.S. (Box 16, Folder 1194)
- One Little Dream of Love (Box 4, Folder 331)
- One Little Raindrop (Box 3, Folder 250)
  Also composed by Jack Meskill and Jean Schwartz
- One Sweet Day, 1919; 22 p. (Box 2, Folder 132)
- One Sweetly Solemn Thought (Box 4, Folder 363)
- One Wonderful Night (Box 7, Folder 651)
- Only a Song (Box 2, Folder 166)
- Only a Song (Box 4, Folder 335)
- Only a Year Ago, Albers, Fred G.; Sam Fox Publishing Co.; Zamecnik, J.S. (Box 16, Folder 1202)
- Ononono (Box 1, Folder 41)
- On the Beach at Waikiki (Box 9, Folder 876)
- On the Curb (Box 9, Folder 798)
- Onward Christian Soldiers (Box 4, Folder 363)
- Ooh, That Kiss (Box 4, Folder 359)
- Operatic Rag (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Orange and Black March (Box 4, Folder 315)
- Orange Blossom Rag (Box 3, Folder 237)
  Also composed by Anton Lada and Joe Cawley
- Noure et Anitra. Orgies of the Spirits, 1917; Il'inskii, A. (Aleksandr); Jungnickel, Ross (Box 16, Folder 1190)
  On item: Artist's Orchestra Repertoir, no. 67
- Oriental (Box 1, Folder 89)
- Oriental-Caravan-Procession (Box 5, Folder 481)
  From Carl Fischer "Film Themes"
- Oriental Dancing Girls (Box 1, Folder 81)
- Oriental Dancing Girls (Box 1, Folder 81)
- Oriental Drama. Prelude (Box 6, Folder 547)
- Oriental Drama. Prelude (Box 6, Folder 550)
- Oriental Love Dream (Box 8, Folder 717)
  Also composed by Earl Burtnett and Henry Miller.
- Oriental Moon (Box 8, Folder 720)
  Also composed by Leo Flanders.
- Oriental Scene-Caravan-or Dance (Box 4, Folder 387)
- Oriental Scene-Dance (Box 8, Folder 753)
- Oriental Scene-Plaintive-Pleading, 1924; 14 p. (Box 5, Folder 392)
- Oriental Scene-Pleading-Narrative (Box 1, Folder 95)
- Oriental Scene-Song-Dance (Box 1, Folder 97)
- Orpheus in der Unterwelt (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Ouch! (Box 6, Folder 504)
- Our Commodore (Box 4, Folder 312)
- Our Country First (Box 4, Folder 323)
- Our Girlies (Box 4, Folder 303)
- Our God, Save To Us Our Sultan (Box 9, Folder 844)
  Turkish hymn
- Our Starry Flag (Box 4, Folder 309)
- Out Of Nowhere, 1931; 14 p. (Box 2, Folder 202)
- Over the Waves (Box 9, Folder 786)
- Over There! (Box 6, Folder 507)
- Overture Miniature from The Nut Cracker Suite (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Oyama, 1914 (Box 9, Folder 831)
- Pahjamah (Box 8, Folder 715)
  Also composed by D. Onivas.
- Pal of My Cradle Days (Box 8, Folder 746)
- Panama Twilight (Box 5, Folder 462)
- Panamericana (Box 11, Folder 943)
- Panama Pacific (Box 4, Folder 317)
- Parade of the Templars, Arbogast, Walter K.; 20 p. (Box 5, Folder 431)
- Paragraph III Overture, 1895; 14 parts (Box 13)
- Parfum d'Amour (Box 7, Folder 672)
- Parlor Comedy. Prelude, 1924; 20 p. (Box 2, Folder 162)
- Passing the Cotton Fields (Box 11, Folder 950)
- Passing of Salome (Box 1, Folder 88)
- A Pathetic Story (Box 1, Folder 33)
- The Path of Glory, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 441)
- The Pathfinder of Panama, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 437)
- Patches (Box 3, Folder 232)
  Also composed by J. Will Callahan
- Pathetic Andante No. 1 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Pathetic Melody (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Peasant Dance-Tarantelle, 15 p. (Box 5, Folder 401)
- Peace with Honor (Box 4, Folder 326)
- Peacock Strut (Box 7, Folder 598)
- Pearls of My Soul. Reverie Religieuse, 1925; 17 parts (Box 13)
- The Pearl Fishers. Selections (Box 36, Folder 8)
- La Peche Valse (Box 7, Folder 645)
- Peer Gynt Suite, 1898 (Box 12, Folder 1018)
- La Pepita Intermezzo, 1910; 13 parts (Box 13)
- Pepita (Box 6, Folder 511)
- A Perfect Day (Box 3, Folder 248)
- Persian Princess (Box 8, Folder 775)
- The Perfect Day. Hosanna, 1901; 12 parts (Box 14)
- A Perfect Day (Box 8, Folder 699)
- Period Costume Pictures. Prelude, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 479)
- Persian Dance (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Persian Lamb Rag (Box 1, Folder 56)
- La Petite Duchesse. Gavotte Louis XV, 1921; 16 parts (Box 13)
- Peter Gink (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Piccalilli Rag (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Pierrot and Pierrette (Box 3, Folder 292)
- Pining, 1919; 12 p. (Box 2, Folder 133)
  Also composed by Fred W. Pike.
- Pitter Patter, 10 p. (Box 2, Folder 184)
- Pizzicato - Mysterioso (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Plaintive Melody-Lullaby, 1924 (Box 9, Folder 888)
- Plaintive (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Plaintive Narrative-Mother Story-Lullaby (Box 4, Folder 389)
- Play Ball (Box 6, Folder 508)
- Please Go Away and Let Me Sleep (Box 9, Folder 860)
  Inside cover has black and white film announcement for "Flirting With Fate" starring Douglas Fairbanks.
- The Poachers Overture. Les Braconniers, 1913; 16 parts (Box 13)
- Le Poeme (Box 7, Folder 670)
- Pointsetta (Box 3, Folder 291)
  Also composed by Mae Davis.
- A Polish Dance Theme (Box 1, Folder 103)
- Polonaise Militaire (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Pomp and Circumstance (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Pomposo (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Powder and Patches (Box 1, Folder 99)
- Pozieres (Box 4, Folder 324)
- Pregando (Box 4, Folder 369)
- Prelude, 1925; Beghon, Jean; Carl Fischer Inc.; Roberts, Charles J. (Box 16, Folder 1236)
- Prelude, op. 28, no. 15, 1912; Chopin, Frédéric; G. Schirmer, Inc.; Hinrichs, Gustav (Box 16, Folder 1208)
  On item: Orch. Miscellany, no. 9
- Prelude Heroique, op. 25, 1923; Kempinski, Leo A.; Music Buyers Corp. (Box 16, Folder 1234)
- Pres de Toi (Near Thee) (Box 9, Folder 785)
- Presto (Box 8, Folder 772)
- The Prince of Peace is King, 1901; 12 parts (Box 13)
- A Prohibition Episode (Box 7, Folder 626)
- Processional-Festival-March-Jubilation (Box 5, Folder 482)
  Selections by Chas. J. Roberts. From Carl Fischer "Film Themes"
- Processional (Box 6, Folder 490)
- Procrastination Rag (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Prosperity Rag (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Puppchen (Box 3, Folder 284)
- Purity (Box 1, Folder 23)
- The Racooon and the Bee (Box 9, Folder 819)
- Rachety Coo! (Box 7, Folder 603)
  from "Katinka."
- Radio Keith Orpheum Broadcasting Signature March
  Also composed by Thos. Kennedy.
- Radio Message (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Rag Baby Rag (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Rag-a-Minor (Box 6, Folder 505)
- The Ragtime Bassplayer, 1913; 18 p. (Box 2, Folder 193)
- The Ragtime Pipe of Pan (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Rain of Pearls, 1916 (Box 9, Folder 827)
- The Rainbow March (Box 9, Folder 795)
- Ram Rod Rag, 1911; 14 p. (Box 2, Folder 182)
- Red Devil (Box 1, Folder 75)
- Red Raven Rag, 21 p. (Box 2, Folder 194)
- Redemption, 1925; 19 parts (Box 14)
- The Red Rose Rag, 20 p. (Box 2, Folder 188)
- The Red Tulip (Box 7, Folder 636)
- The Red Bandana Rag, 1913; 10 p. (Box 2, Folder 197)
- Redskin (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Regimental Songs (Box 8, Folder 779)
- Reindeer Rag, 1915; 15 p. (Box 2, Folder 179)
- Repentance (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Rescue the Perishing (Box 4, Folder 363)
- Resignation (Box 4, Folder 370)
- Le Retour, 1911; 14 parts (Box 13)
- Reuben on Parade (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Reverie Waltz (Box 8, Folder 778)
- Rhapsodie Norvegienne (Norwegian Rhapsody), 1916 (Box 12, Folder 974)
- Rhapsodie Hongroise No.13, 1922; 21 parts (Box 14)
- Rhinoceros Rag, 1912; 15 p. (Box 2, Folder 183)
- The Ringmaster (Box 8, Folder 760)
- Riverside Rag (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Rock a Bye Baby (Box 9, Folder 856)
- Rock-a-Bye Baby, 1922 (Box 9, Folder 884)
- Roll On, Mississippi, Roll On (Box 3, Folder 259)
  Also composed by James McCaffrey and Dave Ringle.
- Romany Love, 20 p. (Box 5, Folder 419)
  Hotel orchestra arrangement.
- Romance, from the incidental music to "The Conqueror", 1906 (Box 12, Folder 1021)
- Romance in F (Box 4, Folder 373)
- Rosemary, 1915 (Box 9, Folder 826)
- Roses of Picardy (Box 8, Folder 748)
- The Rosary (Box 4, Folder 364)
- Rose Leaf Rag (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Rose of China (Box 6, Folder 545)
  Also composed by Clark Tyler.
- Rose of Spain (Box 6, Folder 516)
  Also composed by Billy Fazioli and Ray Miller.
- Roses from the South (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Roses and Violets (Box 7, Folder 629)
- Round of Country Dance Tunes, A, 1926; G. Schirmer, Inc.; Schmid, Adolf; Berliner, Dorothy (Box 15, Folder 1144)
  Galaxy, no. 300.
- Rubber Plant Rag, 1919; 19 p. (Box 2, Folder 178)
- Rube Stories. Prelude (Box 8, Folder 729)
- Le Ruisseau, 1925; 17 parts (Box 13)
- Rule Brittania (Box 9, Folder 871)
- Russian Romance (Box 9, Folder 846)
- Russian Pony Rag (Box 1, Folder 77)
- Russian Rag (Box 3, Folder 249)
- Russian-Arab-Dervish (Box 1, Folder 98)
- Sailor Song Chant (Box 9, Folder 869)
- Salut D'Amour (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Salve Regina. Christmas Morning, 1901; 12 parts (Box 13)
- Sambo's Holiday (Box 11, Folder 956)
- San (Box 6, Folder 542)
- Sandy River Rag, 1913; 16 p. (Box 2, Folder 171)
- Sans Souci (Box 6, Folder 526)
- Sarabande (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Satyr Dance, from the incidental music to "The Conqueror", 1906 (Box 12, Folder 1021)
- Savannah (Box 3, Folder 273)
- Save By the Blood (Box 4, Folder 363)
- Scaramouche (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Scenes Pittoresques, Angelus and Fete Boheme, 1907 (Box 12, Folder 982)
- Scenes de Ballet, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 1015)
- School Days (Box 9, Folder 885)
- Scotch Pastorale, 1923; Carl Fischer Inc.; Roberts, Charles J.; Saenger, Gustav (Box 15, Folder 1159)
  Op. 103, no. 2.
- See Dixie First (Box 10, Folder 912)
- See-Saw Waltz (Box 4, Folder 308)
- Semper Fidelis March (Box 9, Folder 816)
- Seminola (Box 1, Folder 50)
  Also composed by Robert King.
- Semiramide (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Serenade, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 980)
- Serio-Comic (Burlesque on "Hero" Themes), 1924; 16 p. (Box 5, Folder 407)
- La Serenata de la Argentina (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Serenade Coquette (Box 4, Folder 374)
- Serenade for String Orchestra, Op.48. Waltz (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Sheridan's Ride (Box 8, Folder 761)
- The Sheik of Araby (Box 8, Folder 719)
- Sheep and Goat (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Shimmy - Nods from Chaminade (Box 3, Folder 223)
- Short Trumpet Calls (Box 9, Folder 882)
- Shoulder to Shoulder (Box 4, Folder 320)
- Sicilian Chimes (Box 4, Folder 365)
- Sierra Morena, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 446)
- Sierra Lunar (Box 6, Folder 515)
- Silver Fox (Box 9, Folder 847)
- Silver Sands of Hawaii, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 459)
  Also composed by Monte Carlo and Louis Breau
- The Silver Bell (Box 8, Folder 763)
- Sinbad (Box 8, Folder 754)
  Also composed by Al Jolsom.
- Since You Went Away, 1926; 20 p. (Box 2, Folder 124)
- Since You Went Away, 1926; 20 p. (Box 2, Folder 124)
- Sing Me Love's Lullaby (Box 7, Folder 625)
- Sir Henry March (Box 7, Folder 660)
- Siren (Box 5, Folder 467)
- The Skaters (Box 4, Folder 304)
- The Skyrocket (Box 8, Folder 757)
- Sleep (Box 7, Folder 627)
- Sleeping Beauty, 1925; Beghon, Jean; Carl Fischer Inc.; Roberts, Charles J. (Box 16, Folder 1239)
- The Smiler (A Joplin Rag), 1907; 13 p. (Box 2, Folder 181)
- Smilin' Through (Box 4, Folder 339)
- Snappin' Turtle (Box 3, Folder 229)
- The Sneak (Box 3, Folder 221)
- Soldiers of Fortune, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 686)
- Solid Men to the Front (Box 7, Folder 662)
- Solitude (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Somewhere A Voice is Calling (Box 8, Folder 703)
- Some Boy (Box 3, Folder 225)
  Also composed by Dave Stamper
- Some Day They're Coming Home Again (Box 6, Folder 495)
- Sometime (Box 7, Folder 610)
  Also composed by Ted Fiorito.
- Sonata, F# minor, op. 11. Aria, 1913; G. Schirmer, Inc.; Schumann, Robert; Vecsey, Armand (Box 16, Folder 1229)
- Songs From Schakespear's Time, 1916; Borch, Gaston; G. Schirmer, Inc. (Box 15, Folder 1148)
  No. 186G in the Schirmer Galaxy series.
- Songs of the Sea (Box 8, Folder 780)
- Sons of Britain March, 1915; 18 p. (Box 5, Folder 432)
- Song of Persia (Persian Rug Song) (Box 1, Folder 94)
- Songs of Scotland: Grand Selection of Scottish Folk Songs and Dances, 1913; Jerome H. Remick & Co.; Lampe, J. B. (Jens Bodewalt) (Box 15, Folder 1147)
- Sons of Veterans March, 10 p. (Box 5, Folder 427)
- Songe D'Amour (Dream of Love) (Box 1, Folder 82)
- Sons of Uncle Sam (Box 4, Folder 329)
- A Southern Wedding (Box 10, Folder 910)
- Sounds from the Cloister, 1925; 20 parts (Box 14)
- Sounds From the Sunny South, 1912 (Box 11, Folder 947)
- Sourire d'Avril (Box 9, Folder 783)
- The Southlanders, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 442)
- Souvenir d'Antan = Memories of Yesteryears, 1923; Baron, Henry; Belwin, Inc. (Box 16, Folder 1242)
  Edition Artistique no. 6.
- Souvenir Douloureux, 1925; Bicchiere, Rocco; Music Buyers Corp. (Box 16, Folder 1241)
- Spaghetti Rag (Box 1, Folder 71)
- Speech! (Box 7, Folder 623)
  Also composed by Cliff Friend.
- Speed (Box 6, Folder 492)
- Spiritual (Box 11, Folder 952)
- Splivins Corners (Box 8, Folder 725)
- Spring Blossoms, 1920; Belwin, Inc.; Del Castillo, Lloyd G.; Levy, Sol P. (Sol Paul) (Box 16, Folder 1238)
- Spring Flowers, Zamecnik, J.S.; Sam Fox Publishing Co.; Wood, J. Dellinger (Box 15, Folder 1171)
- Spring Song (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Spring Song, Carl Fischer Inc.; Mendelssohn, Felix; Moses, Theo. (Box 16, Folder 1207)
- Springtime (Box 8, Folder 708)
- Springtime of Life, 1925; Marquardt, P.A.; Music Buyers Corp. (Box 16, Folder 1240)
- Springtime Rag, 1916; 13 p. (Box 2, Folder 195)
- The Squad March, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 438)
- The Starry Jack, 1913 (Box 9, Folder 824)
- Starlight Love (Box 7, Folder 633)
- The Statesman (Box 4, Folder 322)
- Step On It (Box 6, Folder 510)
- Storm Galop (Box 8, Folder 756)
- Stop It! (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Stories of Boys. Prelude, 18 p. (Box 2, Folder 161)
- Strawberries (Box 6, Folder 492)
- Suffering of the Innocent-Neglected Orphan Child in distress-or in sick bed (Box 4, Folder 380)
- Suite Ancienne. Prelude, op. 108, 1926; Carl Fischer Inc.; Hadley, Henry; Roberts, Charles J. (Box 16, Folder 1233)
- Suite of Serenades (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Sylvia (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Sunbeams., 1914; 42 pages; Ensemble parts for various instruments (Box 2, Folder 117)
- Sunshine Overture, 1915; 16 parts (Box 13)
- The Sunny South (Box 10, Folder 905)
- Sunapee (Box 4, Folder 330)
- Synchronizing Suite No. 1 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  1a Minor Love Motif
- Sunnyland (Box 3, Folder 287)
- Sur le Flot Berceur (Box 7, Folder 631)
- Swedish Coronation March (Box 11, Folder 968)
- Swedish Processional March (Box 5, Folder 475)
- Sweet Luana, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 473)
- Sweetheart, 1916; 8 p. (Box 2, Folder 128)
- The Sweetest Story Ever Told (Box 8, Folder 705)
- Sweet and Lovely (Box 3, Folder 261)
  Also composed by Harry Tobias and Jules Lemare
- Sweetheart, 1916; 8 p. (Box 2, Folder 128)
- Sweet Greetings (Box 4, Folder 388)
- Sweet Indiana Home (Box 1, Folder 94)
- Sweet Memories (Box 4, Folder 376)
- Sweet Simplicity (Box 6, Folder 564)
- Sweetness (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Sweetheart For You (Box 4, Folder 337)
- Synchronizing Suite No. 1 for Motion Picture Settings (Box 1, Folder 28)
  1 Major Love Motif.
- Ta-Dji-Da (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Take Me Back (Box 5, Folder 565)
- Tanzweise, 1903; 12 parts (Box 14)
- Tangomania (Box 6, Folder 496)
- Tannhauser (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Tar Babies (Box 1, Folder 62)
- The Tarantula (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Tea Leaves (Box 6, Folder 563)
- Tears, 1917; 12 parts (Box 14)
- Teddy Bear Blues (Box 7, Folder 605)
- Tell Me Pretty Maiden (Box 9, Folder 872)
  Handwritten manuscript
- Tempo Di Gavotta, 1918; 19 parts (Box 14)
- Tents of Arabs (Box 8, Folder 723)
- Tete-A-Tete Op.354, 1912; 20 parts (Box 14)
- That Hindu Rag (Box 8, Folder 712)
- That Melody of Love, 1927; 30 p. (Box 2, Folder 121)
  Theme song from the MGM film, " Love," which featured Greta Garbo and John Gilbert.
- That Night in Araby (Box 8, Folder 755)
  Also composed by Ted Snyder.
- That Peculiar Rag, 11 p. (Box 2, Folder 185)
- That Tumble Down Shack in Althone, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 821)
  Also composed by Alma M. Sanders
- That Wonderful Mother of Mine (Box 8, Folder 710)
- That Sneaky Glide, 1912; 14 p. (Box 2, Folder 192)
- That's My Way of Loving You (Box 4, Folder 357)
  Also composed by Billy Hays.
- That's the Song of Songs For Me (Box 6, Folder 566)
- That Stop Time Rag, 1912; 10 p. (Box 2, Folder 198)
- There Is a Happy Land (Box 9, Folder 877)
- There Once Was an Owl, 1904; 12 parts (Box 14)
- They're All Goin' Into the Movies (Box 6, Folder 574)
- Thistle, 1896; Puerner, Charles; Carl Fischer Inc. (Box 15, Folder 1157)
  Selection on Scotch airs. Parts.
- The Thoroughbred (Box 9, Folder 849)
- Thoughts at Twilight. Reverie, 1919; 17 parts (Box 14)
- Those Mem'ry Bells (Box 4, Folder 344)
- Thoughts of Yore, 1925; 17 parts (Box 14)
- Thoughts No. 35 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Three Gems 1. Andante. 2. Reverie. 3. Choral, 1916; 18 parts (Box 14)
- Three Irish Dances (Box 9, Folder 918)
- Three Reveries 1. An Evening Prayer. La Melancholie. Lullaby, 1916; 16 parts (Box 14)
- Three Dances from Tom Jones, No. 1 Morris Dance, 1907 (Box 12, Folder 1019)
- Three Dances from Tom Jones, No. 2 Gavotte, 1907 (Box 12, Folder 1019)
- Three Dances from Tom Jones, No. 3 Jig, 1907 (Box 12, Folder 1019)
- Three French Songs, I. Hindoo Song, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 1013)
- Three French Songs, II. At Evening, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 1013)
- Three French Songs, III. Open Thy Blue Eyes, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 1013)
- Three Songs from Eliland (Box 7, Folder 596)
- Thru' Azure Blue, 1920; 13 parts (Box 14)
- Thru' Azure Blue (Box 34, Folder 7)
- The Thunderer (Box 9, Folder 813)
- The Thunder Cloud (Box 4, Folder 316)
- Ti-O-San (Box 6, Folder 556)
  Also composed by Case, L. Clair.
- Tickle Toes (Box 9, Folder 833)
- To Arms Overture Militaire, 1914; 12 parts (Box 13)
- To Make a Long Story Short (Box 3, Folder 264)
- The Toe Dancer (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Told at Twilight, 1905; 12 parts (Box 14)
- Tom-Tom (Box 1, Folder 87)
  From "Queen of Hearts".
- Top Liner Rag (Box 4, Folder 361)
- Topsy (Box 6, Folder 502)
- Toreador Humoresque (Box 6, Folder 523)
- Torture Theme (Box 9, Folder 883)
- Tout Paris (Box 9, Folder 784)
- Trapeze Galop (Box 8, Folder 769)
- Traumerei, op. 8, Carl Fischer Inc.; Jensen, Adolf; Roberts, Charles J. (Box 16, Folder 1219)
- Traumerei. Am Camin. Susses Sehnen, 1897; 33 parts (Box 13)
- Trees. Love's Sorrow, 1925; 20 parts (Box 14)
- Tres Moutarde (Box 3, Folder 277)
- Tri-Mountain (Box 9, Folder 790)
- Triumph, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 440)
- The Triumph of Old Glory, 1917; 21 p. (Box 5, Folder 413)
- Trouville Canter (Box 7, Folder 599)
- Truly I Do, 1925; 14 p. (Box 2, Folder 123)
- Trumpet Fanfare (Box 9, Folder 881)
- The Trysting Place, 1924; 16 parts (Box 14)
- Tulips, 1916; 12 parts (Box 14)
- Tunisia Intermezzo (Box 6, Folder 580)
- Turkey Trot (Box 8, Folder 726)
- Turkish Towel Rag (Box 1, Folder 74)
- Turn Back The Universe, 1916; 15 p. (Box 2, Folder 140)
- Turandot, 1903 (Box 12, Folder 1023)
- Twelve Scotch Songs, 1902; Carl Fischer Inc.; de Witt, L.O. (Box 15, Folder 1150)
  Contents: Auld Robin Gray, Logie O'Buchan, Ye Banks and Braes O'Bonny Doon, Robin Adair, AFton Water, I Dreamed I Lay, Comin' Thro' the Rye, Within a Mile of Edinbourgh Town, Maid of Dundee, Annie Laurie, Scots Wha Hae wi' Wallace Bled, Auld Lang Syne.
- Twilight. Op.24 No.1 Serenade, 1912; 19 parts (Box 14)
- Twilight Fancies, 1921; 16 parts (Box 14)
- Twilight Musings Op.164, 1919; 18 parts (Box 14)
- Twilight Whispers. Intermezzo Op.202, 1895; 10 parts (Box 14)
- Two Characteristic Dances (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Two Characteristic Themes, 1918; 14 p. (Box 2, Folder 155)
- Two Guitars, 1925; 20 parts (Box 14)
- Two Guitars (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Two Hearts (Box 3, Folder 245)
- Two Lyric Pieces, Waltz and Fairy Dance, 1924 (Box 12, Folder 976)
- Two Sketches No.1. Serenade. No. 2. Romance, 1915; 7 parts (Box 14)
- Ukelele Lou, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 470)
- Un peu d'Amour (Box 8, Folder 707)
- Uncle Josh's Huskin' Dance (Box 8, Folder 732)
- Under the Harvest Moon (Box 10, Folder 932)
- Under the Palm Trees, 1904 (Box 9, Folder 828)
- Under the Stars (Box 1, Folder 104)
- Under the Starry Banner, 1915 (Box 8, Folder 685)
- Underneath Hawaiian Skies, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 460)
  Also composed by Fred Rose
- Undine Overture, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 1024)
- Une Heure D'Amour (Box 7, Folder 634)
- The Valley of Roses (Box 8, Folder 696)
- Valse Annette (Box 3, Folder 290)
- Valse Caprice, Carl Fischer Inc.; Roberts, Charles J.; Rubinstein, Anton (Box 15, Folder 1163)
- Valse Infernale (Box 9, Folder 787)
- Valse Lente, 1913; Carl Fischer Inc.; Delibes, Léo; Roberts, Charles J. (Box 15, Folder 1164)
  From Ballet Sylvia. Parts.
- Valse des Midinettes (Box 7, Folder 647)
- Valse Pathetique (Box 7, Folder 648)
- Valse Peggy (Box 3, Folder 296)
- Valse Romance (Box 7, Folder 637)
- The Vamp (Box 7, Folder 619)
- unspecified (Box 10, Folder 931)
- Vanguard of Democracy, 1918; 10 p. (Box 5, Folder 429)
- Vanity (Box 10, Folder 924)
- La Veeda (Box 6, Folder 519)
- Velvet Lady (Box 7, Folder 611)
- Venetia (Box 10, Folder 923)